

Le Trung Dung

Ç' Male

https://www.facebook.com/dungg.trung .5

Position: Java Intern

19/12/2002

(+84)842824902

Phuc La, Ha Dong, Ha Noi

SUMMARY

The third year student majoring in Software Engineering at FPT University has experience in Java/JSP/Servlet and basic in React web programming. I look forward to leveraging my skills and knowledge to contribute to the company as a ReactJS Intern.

EDUCATION

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING (SPECIALIZED FIELD: NODEJS -REACTJS)

10/2020 - Present

FPT UNIVERSITY - HA NOI

GPA: 3.08/4

EXPERIENCE

DEVELOPER

03/2023 -

<CRUD EMPLOYEE REACTJS>

- The project allow enterprise can manage their employee with basic CRUD function all of data save in Local Storage, The project is used HTML, CSS, JS, JSON on REACTJS platform to do this short project.
- · Github: https://github.com/TrungDung1912/ReactJSCRUD.git

DEVELOPER

04/2023 -

<PLAYER MUSIC G2>

- The small project is done by HTML, CSS, and JS Core. The project allows people who are music nerds can have an individual music area, where all of the list captivating songs help them chill out or let their hair down after tiring days.
- · Github: https://github.com/TrungDung1912/MusicPlayerG2.git

LEADER, DEVELOPER, TESTER

01/2023 - 04/2023

FPT UNIVERSITY - HA NOI < ONLINE DEBIT BOOK>

- Act as the team leader (team of 5 members) throughout the project Successfully designed online debit software allow user can access and CRUD with the debt. The system use Java Servlet, SQL Server, HTML, CSS, JS.
- Manage project progress and divide work, make project reports for members
- Analyze, test, program and write product reports
- Gitlab: https://gitlab.com/maitranhuy1709/SWP_SE1640_GR3.git

DEVELOPER, TESTER

09/2022 - 11/2022

FPT UNIVERSITY - HA NOI < ATTENDANCE SYSTEM>

- Successfully designed attendance software for lecturers and students allow lecture can check attend to the student. The system use Java Servlet, SQL Server, HTML, CSS
- Project progress management
- · Analyze, test and program, write product reports
- Github: https://github.com/TrungDung1912/IOT1601_PRJ301_ASS.git

ADVANCED SKILL

- \cdot Read, Listen, Write, Speak to English document ~ 6.5 IELTS
- · Gitlab/ Github
- · Apache Netbeans IDE 13 / Apache Tomcat 8.5
- Microsoft SQL Server Management Studio 18

AWARDS

Excellent student of the term: Fall2022

FPT University Scholarship: 70%

BASIC SKILL

- Teamwork
- · Flexible / Adaptable
- · Diligent / Perfectionist / Careful
- Communication

CERTIFICATES

CertNexus Certified Ethical Emerging Technologist

01/2023

Software Development Lifecycle from the University of Minnesota

09/2022

Web Design for Everybody: Basic of Web Development & Coding from University of Michigan

06/2022

Computer Communications from University of Colorado System

01/2022

Academic Skills for University Success from the University of Sydney

09/2021

ACTIVITY

LOGISTICS BOARD

11/2020 - 11/2022

VNEXPRESS MARATHON HANOI

The volunteer of VnExpress Marathon Hanoi Midnight 2020 / 2022

LOGISTICS BOARD
10/2020 - Present

CULTURE BOARD

02/2021 - 03/2021

F-CAMP FPTU

The logistic board of Fcamp 2020 / 2021/ 2022/ 2023

VỊ TẾT FPTU

The culture board of Vị tết 2021